CHRISTY VASUDEVAN

Graphic Designer

Graphic Design Specialist with 5+ years of experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Expert at interdepartmental coordination and communication.

Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite (illustrator, Photoshop, inDesign), Microsoft Office suite, and web design applications (HTML, CSS).



EDUCATION

DIPLOMA CSE

Dr. Dharmambal Govt. Polytechnic College

■ B.E Computer Science

Meenakshi College of Engineering

C-Tech Graphic Designing

Image Creative Education

WORK EXPERIENCE

Gharuda infotech Pvt Ltd

Web Designer 2016-2017



Designed static pages using div, CSS and jquery and created dynamic pages for case studies, common issues, and popular knowledge transfer also applied basic organic SEO rules and performed cross browser testing and solved all issues. Tools and technology used mostly HTML, CSS, Javascript, jquery.

Wipro Technologies

Graphic Designer 2018-2019



Designed Advertisement for Magazine and Yellow page book advertisement designed for foreign countries and also We interact directly with clients in order to update advertisements.

Foodhub Software Solutions Pvt Ltd

Graphic Designer 2019-2021



Designed Creative ads, Menu card, brochures, poster, display ads and landing pages for UK, USA & Ireland clients. Developed landing pages and Mailer using HTML5, CSS. Creating Mailer Design using Dot digital, Mailchimp & Zoho campaigns. Creating 2D character using Adobe illustrator

HCL Technologies

Graphic Designer 2021-Till Now

HCLTech

Updating labels as per redline document based on branded guidelines. Updating labels & IFU's using Adobe illustrator and InDesign. Creating label (unit, shelf, case carton)/IFU redline, graphics update, proofing and final review. Preparing labeling Master sheet/tracker with dashboard in excel. Performing gap assessment against MDR (2017/745)/IVDR (2017/746) requiremnt & ISO.

SKILL



















LANGUAGES

TAMIL ENGLISH

BEHANCE

MALAYALAM

https://www.behance.net/christvsuman

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS



Shuttle



Music



Travel



Cooking

Photography

CONTACT US

- christylediya@gmail.com
- 7550181554
- 16.06.93
- Married
- Thambaram, Chennai